Agenitc development is powerful, but scaling what one person can do
on their laptop to a repeatable process across your team and large code bases...
that gets tricky.
In this upcoming webinar, we'll talk about common failure scenarios
when scaling agentic development and what can you do about them.
Spoiler alert: a lot of that comes down to context.
We’ll mention common use cases for context, like rolling out
policies and best practices or documenting your platform,
and we will discuss how the context development lifecycle
connects to the software development lifecycle and how it can scale.
If that sounds interesting, follow the link to register.
I hope to see you there.